

Andrei Dominick A. Randall

Web Developer

Hello, I'm Andrei, I'm a fresh graduate, and a self-taught website developer with 2 years of experience in the field, I can create websites using html, css, basic js and with different programming languages also known as native coding.

Contact Info

+639672278242

✓ andreirandall@gmail.com

https://baktot.github.io/

Education

AMACC Gensan (College)
2018 - 2023

AMACC Gensan (Senior Highschool)
2016 - 2018

San Bartolome National Highschool 2012 - 2016

Banaad Elementary School 2006 - 2012

Skills

Front End Development

-html, css, js

Back End Development

-database management

PHP (Laravel Framework)

-proficient programming language

Work Experience

Freelancer (Programming)

2022 - 2023

Become a freelancer and accepting programming projects such as simple blog site, simple management system and other projects that I'm able to build.

Web Developer
 2022 (half a year)
 Become an Intern web developer at
 RDEX Food International Philippines Inc.,
 Responsible mostly on web design.

Layout Artist

2019 - 2021

Become an Intern layout artist at RFM Printing Press. Responsible mostly in creating layouts for the clients.

For More Information



This Barcode
Redirect to My
Personal Portfolio
baktot.github.io